

MUSAH S.
WEB DEVELOPER

DETAILS

Kano

Nigeria

+2348103855142

simpadnan@gmail.com

SKILLS

SQL

Python

PHP

Wordpress

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

SEO

PROFILE

I am a fullstack web developer, designer, and SEO analyst based in Kano City, Nigeria. I'm a potential problem solver with passion and intensive dedication to work. My skill set is furnished with 3 years of experience working as a Junior fullstack web developer at Quba Tech Group.

I have obtained neccessary skills to pilot great project to brilliant goals. Programming was fun to me until it became a career.

WORK HISTORY

WEB DESIGNER, LOGIC GATE, KADUNA

Mar, 2015 - Nov, 2016

 Designed a website that increased user engagement by 80% through enhanced navigation and improved user experience

BACKEND DEVELOPER, QUBA TECH, KANO

Sep, 2019 - Jul, 2021

 Designed and built a robust and scalable backend architecture that handled up to 5000 concurrent users with minimal downtime

SEO ANALYST, QUBA TECH, KANO

Nov, 2021 - Mar, 2022

 Developed an effective SEO strategy that increased organic search engine rankings and doubled website visits

EDUCATION HISTORY

DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE LOGIC GATE

Jan, 2015 - Feb, 2017

B.SC HUMAN ANATOMY, BAYERO UNIVERSITY KANO

Nov, 2017 - Mar, 2021